Guide to the Eugene V. Dennett Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- EUGENE V. DENNETT PAPERS, 1898-1988; RECORD GROUP I (Box-folder 1/1-19/9)
  - Steelworkers of America, United Local 1208, 1929-1988; Record Subgroup H (Box-folder 6/1-7/1)
    - STEELWORKERS OF AMERICA UNITED LOCAL 1208 MATERIALS, 1929-1988; SERIES I (Box-folder 6/1-7/1)
      - Constitutions and Bylaws, 1949-1982 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Resolution, 1954 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Agreements, 1929-1962 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Grievances, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Conferences and Conventions, 1952-1981 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Campaign Materials, 1954 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Bulletins, 1935-1987 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Newspaper - Steel Labor, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Periodicals, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Pamphlets, Undated (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Clippings, 1954-1984 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Lists, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Notes, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Wage Scales and Rates, 1942-1960 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Incentives, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - U.S. National Labor Relations Board, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Seniority, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Safety Committee, 1949 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Relief Committee for Strike, 1949 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Lost Times, 1982 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Union Election Camp, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Apprenticeships, Undated (Box-folder 7/1)
      - 22-inch Mill, 1953 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Jaye G. Sykes and The Progressive, 1955 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - E.V. Dennett's Expulsion for the United Steelworkers of America, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Libel Suit: E.V. Dennett v. United Steelworkers of America, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1969 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Harriette Dennett, 1910-1949, 1978; Record Subgroup I (Box-folder 8/1-8/6)
    - HARRIETTE DENNETT MATERIALS, 1910-1949, 1978; SERIES I (Box-folder 8/1-8/6)
      - General Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Affidavit, 1949 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Agreement, 1978 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Diary, 1910 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Yearbook - Franklin High School, 1931 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Subject file re: charges brought against Harriett Dennette by Local 35 of the United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1948 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Eugene V. Dennett Personal Papers, Record Subgroup J (Box-folder 8/7-19/9)
    - INCOMING LETTERS, 1929-1988; SERIES I (Box-folder 8/7-8/8)
      - Anderson and Resner (re. Ernest Fox), 1942 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1979 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Consumers' League of New York, 1937 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Egolf, Jeremy R., 1985 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Fields, Gladys, 1944 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Gilland, Elsie (re: Ernest Fox), 1942 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Gladstein, Grossman, and Margolis (attorneys, San Francisco), 1937 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Johnson, Robert, 1933 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - McGovern, George, 1972 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Mine, Mill and Smelter International Union, 1940 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - National Consumers' League, 1937 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Nielson Television Research, 1985 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor Association, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Public Markets, Weights, and Measures Department (New York), 1936 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Rice, Norm, 1988 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Rozeboom, Egbert, 1929 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Seattle City Council, 1986 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Thompson, Isabel, 1964 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - U.S.Social Security Board (Baltimore), 1938 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Valle, Georgette W., 1985 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Walker, Bill, 1985 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Yuma Realty and Investment Company, 1979 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - OUTGOING LETTERS, 1937-1987; SERIES II (Box-folder 8/9-8/10)
      - Letters to Editors, 1955-1987 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1987 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE, 1935-1982; SERIES III (Box-folder 8/11-8/15)
      - Dennett, Herbert (Father), 1935-1951 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Dennett, Lee A., 1978-1986 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Horsley, Marie Dennett, 1981 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Mann, Marvell Dennett, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Simpson, Betty (Second Wife), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1930-1989; SERIES IV (Box-folder 8/16-9/30)
      - Adams, Brock, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Baldock, Elizabeth, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Beijing Review, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1984 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Bonker, Don, 1984 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Burton, W.H., 1935 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - China Books and Periodicals, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Costigan, Barbara, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Costigan, Howard, 1958-1979 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Costigan, Barbara and Howard, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - DeLacy, Hugh, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Dies, Martin, 1958 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1955-1957 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Evans, Daniel J., 1984-1987 (Box-folder 8/29)
      - Formick, Joseph, 1988 (Box-folder 8/30)
      - Freedom Socialist Party, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8/31)
      - Garrett, Dan L., 1955 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Gorton, Slade, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - Grab, Alonzo, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 8/34)
      - Guozi Shudian, China Publications Center (Peking Review), 1964-1979 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - Hansen, George H., 1930 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Hartle, Barbara, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 8/37)
      - Jackson, Henry M., 1971-1982 (Box-folder 8/38)
      - Kennedy, Edward, 1971 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - King County Records and Elections Division, 1980 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Kohler, Margaret, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - London, Mel M., 1985 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Lowry, Mike, 1984 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Magnuson, Warren G., 1937-1980 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Miller, John, 1987 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Mitchell, James, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Mondale, Walter F., 1983 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Richmond, Al, 1982 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Robinson, Earl, 1987 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Samuels, Howard A., 1979-1987 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Sauvage, Lester, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Seattle Police Department, 1979 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Seattle First National Bank, 1956 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Simonton, Mary Jane, 1985 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Smith, Norine, 1988 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Sorrenson, Sverre, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Spellman, John, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Stewart, Earl, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Talmadge, Phil, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - U.S. Labor Department, 1957 (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Valliere, Winifred D., 1962 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - Vaughn, Lillie, 1962 (Box-folder 9/25)
      - Wainer, Nora R., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - Webster, Hugh, 1950-1979 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Weyant, Louise, 1988 (Box-folder 9/28)
      - W. U. Press, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - Anonymous, 1957 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - WRITINGS BY E.V. DENNETT, 1957-1988; SERIES V (Box-folder 9/31-10/15)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Drafts (Part 1 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Drafts (Part 2 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Drafts (Part 3 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 1 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 2 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 3 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 4 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 5 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 6 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 7 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Notes (Part 8 of 8), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Correspondence (Part 1 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Correspondence (Part 2 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Agitprop-The Life of a Working Class Radical - Correspondence (Part 3 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - "My Family Tree - My Mother's Side" (1982), "Prospectus for a New Daily Paper" (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Writing Notes, 1957 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - WRITINGS BY OTHERS, 1932-1982; SERIES VI (Box-folder 10/16-11/6)
      - "Melvin M. London and the Early 1930s Washington State Unemployed Movement: Reminiscence and Documents" edited by Jeremy R. Egolf - CLOSED until publication, c. 1981 (Box-folder 10/16 (VF 1601))
      - Untitled autobiographical work by Isabel Costigan, Undated (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Report from Iron Mountain on the Possibility and Desirability of Peace with introductory material by Leonard C. Lewin, 1967 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Frozen Destiny by Mabel Mae Miller, Undated (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Addresses by Peter A. Bogdanov and Hugh L. Copper at the Luncheon of the American-Russian Chamber of Commerce, 1932 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - "Intelligence ' Raw' NA-1 to 'Cy'", 1944-1945 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Songs and Poems, Undated (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Jokes, Undated (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1955-1982 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - INTERVIEW AND QUESTIONNAIRE, 1942-1986; SERIES VII (Box-folder 11/7-11/8)
      - Interview - E.V. Dennett by Barbara Costigan, 1986 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Questionnaire - FBI, 1942 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - DIARIES, 1935-1967; SERIES VII (Box-folder 11/9-11/14)
      - 3 Volumes (1935-36, 1939), 1935-1939 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - 5 Volumes (1942, 1946, 1948-1950), 1942-1950 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - 5 Volumes (1951-1955) (Box-folder 11/11)
      - 5 Volumes (1956-1960) (Box-folder 11/12)
      - 5 Volumes (1961-1965) (Box-folder 11/13)
      - 2 Volumes (1966-1967) (Box-folder 11/14)
    - PERSONAL AND GENEALOGICAL DOCUMENTS, 1926-1979; SERIES VII (Box-folder 12/1-12/5)
      - Birth Certificate, 1937 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Critic's Reports, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Transcripts, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Diploma, 1958 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Teaching Contracts, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Certificates, 1928-1971 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Passport, 1979 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Divorce Papers (re: Harriette Dennett), 1952 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Genealogical Research - Dennett Family (Part 1 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Genealogical Research - Dennett Family (Part 2 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Genealogical Research - Dennett Family (Part 3 of 3), 1972-1981 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1938-1939; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Financial Records, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - CALENDARS AND ADDRESS BOOK, 1974-1988; SERIES IX (Box-folder 12/7-12/9)
      - Calendars (Part 1 of 2), 1974-1988 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Calendars (Part 2 of 2), 1974-1988 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Address Book, Undated (Box-folder 12/9)
    - PUBLICATIONS, YEARBOOKS, SCRAPBOOKS, 1927-1955; SERIES X (Box-folder 12/10-13/1)
      - Publications, 1937-1954 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Yearbooks - Oregon Normal School (Part 1 of 2), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Yearbooks - Oregon Normal School (Part 2 of 2), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Scrapbooks, 1933-1955 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - CLIPPINGS, 1948-1988; SERIES XI (Box-folder 14/1-14/13)
      - Bryson, Hugh, 1983 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Caughlan, John, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Communism, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Dennett, LaVaun, 1988 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Fraser, Clara, 1988 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Hoff, Heini, 1984 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Korean War, 1952 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Lowry, Mike, Undated (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Pettus, Terry, 1984 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Smith Act, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Letters to Editors - by Dennett, 1955-1981 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Letters to Editors - by others, 1981 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1988 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - LISTS AND MEMORABILIA, 1925; SERIES XII (Box-folder 14/14-14/15)
      - Lists, Undated (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Memorabilia, 1925 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - CLASS NOTES AND TEACHING PLANS, 1929-1931; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 14/16-15/3)
      - Class Notes and Teaching Plans, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Class Notes and Teaching Plans, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Class Notes and Teaching Plans, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Class Notes and Teaching Plans, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - NOTES, Undated; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 15/4-15/8)
      - Reading Notes (Part 1 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Reading Notes (Part 2 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Reading Notes (Part 3 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Reading Notes (Part 4 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/7)
      - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box-folder 15/8)
    - PHOTOGRAPHS, Undated; SERIES XV (Box-folder 15/9-15/12)
      - Photographs (Part 1 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/9)
      - Photographs (Part 2 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Photographs (Part 3 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Photographs (Part 4 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 15/12)
    - SUBJECT SERIES, 1932-1988; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 15/13-18/11)
      - Adams, Brock, 1987 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - Birnie, Helen, 1956 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - Bonker, Don, 1984 (Box-folder 15/15)
      - Costigan, Howard, 1939-1978 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1957 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - Evans, Daniel J., 1987 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - Fox, Earnest, Undated (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1988 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Gorton, Slade, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 15/21)
      - Grieve, Bob, 1988 (Box-folder 15/22)
      - Kennedy, Edward M., 1971 (Box-folder 15/23)
      - Knaisky, Alex, 1942 (Box-folder 15/24)
      - Magnuson, Warren G., 1971 (Box-folder 15/25)
      - McCarty, Bertel, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 15/26)
      - Moore, Jim, 1988 (Box-folder 15/27)
      - Mori, Hazel, 1951 (Box-folder 15/28)
      - Schultz, "Dutch" - CLOSED, 1966 (Box-folder 15/29 (VF 1601))
      - Smith, Norine, 1988 (Box-folder 15/30)
      - Wainer, Nora R., 1982 (Box-folder 15/31)
      - Whitebook, Oscar, 1955 (Box-folder 15/32)
      - American Atheist Addiction Recovery Group, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 15/33)
      - American Atheists, Puget Sound Chapter, 1988 (Box-folder 15/34)
      - American Civil Liberties Union, 1954-1987 (Box-folder 15/35)
      - China Trip (Part 1 of 3), 1979 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - China Trip (Part 2 of 3), 1979 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - China Trip (Part 3 of 3), 1979 (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Community Medical Services, 1967 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Hugh Delacy Memorial, 1988 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - King County Medical Service, 1949 (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Marine Workers Industrial Union, 1932 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1945 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - E.V. Dennett's military discharge, 1940-1987 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - E.V. Dennett's military commendation, 1945 (Box-folder 16/10)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 16/11)
      - National Labor Relations Act, 1947 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Older Americans Act, 1947 (Box-folder 16/13)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Part 1 of 4), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Part 2 of 4), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Part 3 of 4), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Part 4 of 4), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Pacific Northwest Marxist Scholars' Conference, 1986 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Pacific Northwest Writers' Conference, 1957 (Box-folder 16/19)
      - People's Party, 1945 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Railroad Brotherhood's Unity Movement, 1933 (Box-folder 16/21)
      - Ration Forms, 1942 (Box-folder 16/22)
      - Seattle Model City Program (Part 1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16/23)
      - Seattle Model City Program (Part 2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - Seattle Model City Program (Part 3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16/25)
      - Small Taxpayers Association, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - Smith Act Trial (U.S. v. Huff, et al), 1952 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Socialist Party of America, 1940-1987 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Socialist Workers Party, 1983 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Unemployment, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 17/4)
      - United Farmers' League (Superior, WI), Undated (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 1 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 2 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 3 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 4 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 5 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 6 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 7 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 8 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 9 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 10 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/15)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 11 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/16)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 12 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - Investigation Hearings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee (Part 13 of 13), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 17/18)
      - Hearings on Communist Methods of Infiltration - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Writings - U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - Interrogation of E.V. Dennett - U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service (Part 1 of 2), 1956 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Interrogation of E.V. Dennett - U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service (Part 2 of 2), 1956 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Miscellaneous - U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1949-1963 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - U.S. Naval Supply Depot (re: E.V. dennett's civilian access pass), 1966-1988 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - U.S. Works Progress Administration, 1937 (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Western Oregon State College - Reunions (Part 1 of 2), 1978-1988 (Box-folder 18/6)
      - Western Oregon State College - Reunions (Part 2 of 2), 1978-1988 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Western Oregon State College - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - Woodworkers of America, International (incl. minutes) (Part 1 of 2), 1940-1987 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Woodworkers of America, International (incl. minutes) (Part 2 of 2), 1940-1987 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Workers Ex-Servicemen's League, Undated (Box-folder 18/11)
    - EPHEMERA AND MISCELLANEOUS, 1912-1988; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 18/12-19/9)
      - Ephemera, Undated (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Labor Miscellaneous (Part 1 of 4), 1912-1955 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Labor Miscellaneous (Part 2 of 4), 1912-1955 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Labor Miscellaneous (Part 3 of 4), 1912-1955 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Labor Miscellaneous (Part 4 of 4), 1912-1955 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Political Issues and Campaigns Miscellaneous (Part 1 of 3), 1940-1988 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Political Issues and Campaigns Miscellaneous (Part 2 of 3), 1940-1988 (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Political Issues and Campaigns Miscellaneous (Part 3 of 3), 1940-1988 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Health Miscellaneous (Part 1 of 4), 1946-1988 (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Health Miscellaneous (Part 2 of 4), 1946-1988 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Health Miscellaneous (Part 3 of 4), 1946-1988 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Health Miscellaneous (Part 4 of 4), 1946-1988 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Communist Party (Duplicates for Display Purposes), Undated (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Inlandboatmen's Union (Duplicates for Display Purposes), Undated (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Miscellaneous (Duplicate for Display Purposes), Undated (Box-folder 19/9)